#### Contact

4202 Parry Dr Pearland, TX 77584 2818711118 (Mobile) patrickermis@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/patrickermis (LinkedIn) www.texaslibertytravel.com (Company)

### Top Skills

Healthcare

Hospitals

**HIPAA** 

### Certifications

Trauma Certified Registered Nurse Emergency Nursing Pediatric Course - Course Director

Trauma Nursing Core Course - Course Director

# Patrick Ermis MSN-Ed RN LP TCRN

Clinical Manager II at Memorial Hermann CCC EC League City Pearland, Texas

## Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with Emergency Department background. Course Director for Trauma Nursing Core Course (TNCC) and Emergency Nursing Pediatric Course (ENPC) through the Emergency Nurses Association (ENA). Skilled in Nursing Management, Performance Improvement, Emergency Medicine, EMS Management, and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong entrepreneurship professional with a Bachelor of Science in Nursing (BSN) from The University of Texas at Arlington and a Masters of Science in Nursing - Education (MSN-Ed) from West Coast University

## Experience

Memorial Hermann Convenient Care Center League City Clinical Manager II Emergency Center October 2017 - Present (2 years 10 months) League City, Texas

San Jacinto College
Part Time Faculty - Nursing
January 2019 - Present (1 year 7 months)
South Campus

AE Sophisticated Style
Co-Owner
November 2018 - Present (1 year 9 months)
Pearland, Texas

Texas Liberty Travel
Owner
December 2007 - Present (12 years 8 months)

Texas Liberty Computers Owner November 1998 - October 2018 (20 years)

Western Governors University
Adjunct Clinical Faculty
May 2016 - May 2018 (2 years 1 month)
Houston, Texas

Memorial Hermann Southeast Staff/Charge RN ER August 2014 - October 2017 (3 years 3 months)

East Houston Regional Medical Center 4 years 8 months

Nurse Manager - Emergency Department November 2011 - August 2014 (2 years 10 months) Houston, TX

Staff Nurse\Charge Nurse
January 2010 - November 2011 (1 year 11 months)

Bay Star Ambulance Service
District Manager / Licensed Paramedic
January 2007 - December 2009 (3 years)

Safeway

Field Services Technician January 2000 - January 2007 (7 years 1 month)

Rural/Metro Corporation
Paramedic
June 1996 - January 2000 (3 years 8 months)

Randall's Food and Pharmacy Service Manager June 1991 - June 1996 (5 years 1 month)

Education

Walden University

Doctor of Nursing Practice - DNP · (2020 - 2022)

West Coast University

MSN, Education · (2016 - 2018)

The University of Texas at Arlington

Bachelor of Science in Nursing (BSN), Nursing · (2010 - 2016)

San Jacinto College

ADN, Nursing · (2007 - 2009)

San Jacinto College

Cert of Tech, EMS · (1994 - 1996)